🎵 살아계신 주 나의 참된 소망 (Living Hope) - 찬양 전주
Living Hope - Phil Wickham (Intro)
[1절] 우리와 하나님 사이의 깊은 죄의 심연, 넘을 수 없던 높은 산
How great the chasm that lay between us, How high the mountain I could not climb
절망 속에서 하늘을 바라보며, 어두운 밤 주의 이름을 불렀네
In desperation I turned to heaven, and spoke Your name into the night
어둠을 뚫고 주의 인자하심이 내 영혼의 그림자를 찢으셨네
Then through the darkness Your loving kindness, tore through the shadows of my soul
모든 사역 다 이루시고 승리의 결말 기록하셨네, 예수 그리스도 나의 참된 소망!
The work is finished the end is written, Jesus Christ my living hope
[2절] 그 크신 자비를 누가 상상이나 할 수 있으며, 한량없는 은혜를 어떤 마음이 헤아리랴
Who could imagine so great a mercy? What heart could fathom such boundless grace?
영원하신 하나님 영광 버리고 내려오사, 내 죄와 수치를 대신 짊어지셨네
The God of ages stepped down from glory, to wear my sin and bear my shame
십자가가 말씀하시네 '너는 용서받았노라', 만왕의 왕이 날 주의 자녀라 부르시네
The cross has spoken I am forgiven, the King of kings calls me His own
아름다우신 구주여 난 영원히 주의 것, 예수 그리스도 나의 참된 소망!
Beautiful Savior I'm Yours forever, Jesus Christ my living hope!
[후렴] 할렐루야! 나를 자유케 하신 주를 찬양해!
Hallelujah, praise the One who set me free!
할렐루야! 사망 권세 내게서 힘을 잃었네!
Hallelujah, death has lost its grip on me!
주 모든 사슬 끊으셨고, 주의 이름에 구원이 있네, 예수 그리스도 나의 참된 소망!
You have broken every chain, there's salvation in Your name, Jesus Christ my living hope!
[3절] 약속을 인치시는 그 부활의 아침이 밝았네, 무덤에 묻히셨던 주의 몸이 숨쉬기 시작하셨네!
Then came the morning that sealed the promise, Your buried body began to breathe!
침묵을 깨고 포효하는 유다의 사자, '무덤은 더 이상 그에게 권세 없노라' 선포하셨네!
Out of the silence the roaring Lion declared the grave has no claim on me!
예수님 주께서 승리하셨습니다!
Jesus, Yours is the victory!
[후렴 절정] 할렐루야! 나를 자유케 하신 주를 찬양해! 사망 권세 무너졌네!
Hallelujah, praise the One who set me free! Death has lost its grip on me!
주 모든 사슬 끊으셨고 주의 이름에 구원이 있네, 예수 그리스도 나의 참된 소망!
You have broken every chain, there's salvation in Your name, Jesus Christ my living hope!
🕊️ 부활이요 생명 되신 예수 그리스도, 나의 영원한 소망을 찬양합니다 · 아멘
Jesus Christ, You Are My Living Hope Forever · Amen